<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <dimen name="activity_horizontal_margin">16dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="activity_vertical_margin">16dp</dimen>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app_name">Navigate Sample</string>
    <string name="galaxy_gear">The Samsung Galaxy Gear is a smartwatch produced by Samsung
        Electronics in the Samsung Gear family of devices. Unveiled during a Samsung Unpacked event in Berlin, Germany on
        September 4, 2013, the device serves as a companion for all Samsung Galaxy smartphones and tablets which run Android
        4.3 or newer; it was released on September 25, 2013. \n \nSource: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samsung_Galaxy_Gear</string>
    <string name="galaxy_smart_phone">Brilliant Samsung phone screens
        bring videos and images to life. Super AMOLED displays integrate the layer that detects touch into the screen and
        reflect less light than previous displays. With these screens, everything appears brighter, clearer
        and more captivating. And the display will automatically adjust to lighting conditions. \n \nSource: http://www.bestbuy.com/site/mobile-cell-phones/samsung-galaxy/pcmcat305200050001.c?id=pcmcat305200050001</string>
    <string name="galaxy_tab">The Samsung Galaxy Tab 10.1 is an Android-based
        tablet computer designed and manufactured by Samsung, introduced in 2011. It is part of the Samsung Galaxy Tab
        series, and features a 10.1-inch display and a 1 GHz dual-core Nvidia Tegra 2 processor. \n \nSource: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samsung_Galaxy_Tab_10.1</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="iPad">The iPad is a 9.7 inch touch screen tablet PC made by Apple . The iPad is basically a netbook
        without a keyboard. It has a multi-touch LED-backlit 9.7 x 7.5 inch front display and weighs 1.5 pounds, with a battery that lasts up to ten hours. \n \nSource: http://searchmobilecomputing.techtarget.com/definition/iPad</string>
    <string name="iPhone">The iPhone 5 and 5s had the same screen resolution as the iPhone 4. The iPhone 6, released in September 2014, provided a larger 4.7" display with 1334x750 pixels. The iPhone 6 Plus, released at the same time, came with an even larger 5.5-inch 1920x1080 pixel display. \n \nSource: https://techterms.com/definition/iphone</string>
    <string name="iPod">The iPod is a line of portable media players and multi-purpose pocket computers
        designed and marketed by Apple Inc. The first version was released on October 23, 2001, about 8½ months after iTunes (Macintosh version) was released. \n \nSource: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPod</string>
    <string name="title_activity_child">Child Activity</string>
    <style name="AppBaseTheme" parent="android:Theme.Light">
        
    </style>
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="AppBaseTheme">
        
    </style>
</resources>